Quizzes = [{'Question': 'Which of the following is classified as having advanced HIV disease?', 'A': 'A seropositive  1 2 year old presenting  with recurrent respiratory tract infections', 'B': 'An ART naive client with a CD4 of 320 cells/ml', 'C': 'A 3 year old regardless  of their CD4 count', 'D': 'An interrupter of treatment with a Viral Load > 1 000 copies/ml', 'Answer': 'A 3 year old regardless  of their CD4 count'},
{'Question': 'Which of the following are true concerning advanced HIV disease:', 'A': 'Greater than 1/3 of all PLHIV initiating ART have Advanced HIV Disease', 'B': 'There has been a stagnation in reduction of HIV related mortality globally in spite of improvements  in ART coverage rates', 'C': 'Approximately 10% of PLHIV initiating  ART with Advanced HIV Disease die within the first 3 months', 'D': 'All are true', 'Answer': 'All are true'},
{'Question': 'Evidence-based interventions to reduce mortality and morbidity associated with Advanced HIV Disease include:', 'A': 'Prompt initiation of anti-Tuberculosis treatment in patients with active TB disease', 'B': 'Systematic screening  for Cryptococcus Antigen (CrAG)', 'C': 'Cotrimoxazole prophylaxis', 'D': 'All of the above', 'Answer': 'All of the above'},
{'Question': 'Which of the following are WHO Clinical Stage 3 conditions:', 'A': 'Persistent  Oral Candidiasis', 'B': 'Unexplained  Chronic Diarrhoea for > 1  month', 'C': 'Pulmonary  Tuberculosis', 'D': 'All of the above are True', 'Answer': 'All of the above are True'},
{'Question': 'Which of the following are known symptoms of Cryptococcal Meningitis:', 'A': 'Loss of Weight', 'B': 'Confusion', 'C': 'Sensitivity to light', 'D': 'B and C are true', 'Answer': 'B and C are true'},
{'Question': 'The most common reason for ART Treatment failure is:', 'A': 'Drug resistance', 'B': 'Poor tolerability  of ART medicines', 'C': 'Poor adherence', 'D': 'Pharmacokinetic reasons e.g. medicine-medicine interactions', 'Answer': 'Poor adherence'},
{'Question': 'The package of care for PLHIV with advanced HIV disease includes all of the following except:', 'A': 'Same day CD4 cell count testing on the day of enrolment into HIV care', 'B': 'Same day serum CrAG if CD4 count  >350ceIIs/mm3', 'C': "ART initiation once any OI's have been identified and treatment begun", 'D': 'TB Preventative therapy for newly enrolled PLHIV screening  negative for TB signs and symptoms', 'Answer': 'Same day serum CrAG if CD4 count  >350ceIIs/mm3'},
{'Question': 'With respect to TB-LAM testing, which of the following is NOT CORRECT:', 'A': 'Seriously ill patients are more likely to be LF-LAM positive', 'B': 'A positive LF-LAM is indicative of latent TB infection', 'C': 'The sensitivity of LF-LAM is higher in patients with lower CD4', 'D': 'Quality Controls for TB-LAM should be done weekly', 'Answer': 'A positive LF-LAM is indicative of latent TB infection'},
{'Question': 'Which of the following describes a seriously ill adult:', 'A': 'A heart rate between 70-80 beats per minute', 'B': 'A respiratory rate greater than 30 breaths per minute', 'C': 'Inability to walk unaided', 'D': 'Only B and C are True', 'Answer': 'Only B and C are True'},
{'Question': 'The following CNS conditions are associated with focal neurological signs except:', 'A': 'Toxoplasmosis', 'B': 'CNS Lymphoma', 'C': 'Herpes Simplex Virus', 'D': 'Cryptococcoma', 'Answer': 'Herpes Simplex Virus'}]